Damn, it's pouring.
[shivers]
I'm cold. I'm so gonna get sick.
Maybe I should just go home.
But what about that awful thing?
ROACHES ARE UNSEEMLY,
SO INSTEAD, CAKE! YOU'RE WELCOME!
[moans]
[sneezes]
Huh?
Hmm.
Uh…
Oh, crap.
-Hey.
-[shrieks]
Are you a runaway?
[scoffs]
No.
[Tsukasa] No judgments,
you need to stay dry out here,
but you do know there's been reports
of a creep in the park the last few days?
What? No way!
[grunts]
[groans]
-Thanks for the head-ups.
-Huh?
Uh, hey, wait.
[grunts]
Keep your hands off!
-Huh?
-Here, take it.
[bright music]
[Riri] Borrow it, return it,
let the sparks fly.
-Mm-mm. No thanks.
-[Tsukasa] Why?
[Anzu] Because then, you'll get drenched.
[Tsukasa] Don't worry.
I live really close.
[grunts]
Seriously!
I already owe you for breaking your phone.
I said it was okay. Just take it.
You're going to
get sick out here like this.
Well, I'm so slow,
I couldn't catch a cold.
[Tsukasa] Your nose is running.
-And you were sneezing earlier.
-It's none of your business, okay?
Stop being so stubborn.
-Ugh, fine! Come to my place.
-Huh! What?
[Tsukasa] I've got an extra umbrella
I was going to toss. You can take that.
[Anzu] Um, but…
Listen, if you're worried about owing me…
[Anzu] Hey…
…then just come on already.
-[Anzu] Oh, okay.
-[Tsukasa] Let's go.
[gasps]
[Anzu] Your hand…
[exclaims]
I'm sorry,
but you took forever to take it.
[Anzu] Hey, wait up!
Now, you're getting wet.
[grunts]
[Anzu] Sorry, you're just really tall.
[Anzu gasps]
There! Problem solved.
-Yeah.
-Come on then.
[Anzu] This is every girl's dream.
A hot guy sharing his umbrella
as you walk shoulder to shoulder
in the rain.
Ugh, I will not give in!
[evil laughter]
[theme music]
#2 IT'S TIME FOR CHILDREN
TO GO TO SLEEP
[Tsukasa] Wait there a sec.
[Anzu] He's hot and he lives alone.
[gulps]
No. I will not fall for this obvious trap.
Just think about
your favorite game characters.
-[sighs happily]
-[Tsukasa] Here.
-[Anzu groans]
-[Tsukasa] You should dry off
before you go.
[Anzu] I've got this.
Hot guy blurring filter.
Yeah, that's better.
[Anzu] Thanks.
Not my business, but why
were you hiding in the park anyway?
[Anzu] Hm, actually, there's this thing
at my place, a ro… ro…
-It's too terrifying. I can't even say it.
-Huh?
Robber?
Much worse, a roach!
[shrieks]
I said it.
You let a bug chase you out of your house?
It's not just "a bug", it was gigantic!
[groans]
My mom usually handles
this sort of thing or my cat,
but my parents moved
overseas for work with the cat.
First, the bug spray was empty,
then, that thing came right for me,
so I ran as fast as I could.
[whimpers]
I forgot my wallet and my phone.
Then it started raining.
Ugh, it's the worst night ever.
[whimpers]
Your face…
[laughs]
-[Anzu] Rude!
-[Tsukasa] I'm sorry.
[Anzu] I thought he was the quiet type
who doesn't smile much but…
That sounds like a nightmare.
-[glass shattering]
-[yells]
No!
He broke down my barrier.
You leave me no choice.
Come forth, Momohiki!
[crackling]
-[meows]
-[gasps]
I guess that explains the mix-match shoes.
[Anzu] It's working! Great job, Momohiki.
-[Tsukasa] Want me to get rid of it?
-Huh?
Want me to get rid of it for you?
You know,
the thing that shall not be mentioned.
-For real?
-[gasps]
[Anzu] No, I'm in too deep already.
No, I got this.
Are you trying to avoid me or something?
[Anzu] What? Of course not!
[Tsukasa] If this is about
breaking my phone, don't worry about it.
I was thinking about
getting a new one, anyway.
Uh, um…
I mean, seriously,
when you outright avoid me like that,
it makes me feel anxious.
[Anzu] "Make me feel anxious"?
Well, if you don't want my help…
No, really… I… need help.
-[Tsukasa] All right, let's go.
-Huh…
[cheerful music]
Here, it's cold. Wear this.
[Momohiki meows]
How does he keep doing that?
-[screaming in anger]
-[moans]
[Tsukasa] So, where is it?
I saw it in the kitchen before.
[Anzu] There's a hot guy in my house.
[Tsukasa] I don't see it.
[Anzu] This is way too ridiculous.
[exclaims]
[suspenseful music]
[shrieks]
-[yells]
-[grunts]
[thudding]
It's right there! It's right there!
My bad, just a lens cap.
Who the heck left that thing here?
[groans]
-Did you just freak out over…
-[both gasp]
[Anzu breathes shakily]
How…
How did we end up like this?
[narrator] Roaches are unseemly,
so instead, cake. You're welcome.
-[shrieks]
-[grunts]
-Go get it! Go get it!
-[Tsukasa grunts, gasps]
[Tsukasa] That bastard!
[Tsukasa grunts]
[grunting continues]
[whimpers]
Piece of cake!
[squeals]
Throw it away! Throw it away!
[rain splatters]
[Anzu] Thanks for helping
and sorry about stepping on you.
[Tsukasa] Seriously, don't mention it.
See you at school, Hoshino.
Wait? How do you know my name?
-Nameplate.
-Oh…
Right.
[chuckles awkwardly]
Tsukasa Kazuki. We go to the same school.
-[Anzu] Right. I'm Class 2.
-I'm Class 7.
Do me a favor, don't avoid me anymore.
[gasps, sucks teeth]
Right.
-Oh, can I at least wash your--
-No. Really. It's fine.
Anyway, it might be a good idea
to take a nice warm bath.
And be sure to bundle up.
Yes, dad.
And you be sure
to eat something hot tonight.
All right, Kazuki?
[Tsukasa] Okay, mom.
[chuckles]
Later.
-[wind whooshing]
-[both gasp]
[effort grunts]
[Tsukasa exhales deeply]
[breathes nervously]
-Guess I could run for it.
-Uh, well, this sucks.
[Tsukasa] I'll be fine. See ya.
-[wind whooshing]
-[grunts]
-[glass shatters]
-[both yelp]
Officials are expecting
the storm to last all night.
A city-wide warning is in effect.
People have been asked to remain indoors,
and avoid driving
in these severely dangerous conditions.
[sighs]
Well, that's just great.
A DREAM HOME
[Anzu] This is my mom
and dad's dream house, their forever home.
And they totally entrusted me
to take care of it while they're gone.
Now, look at it!
Not only does this freaky weather
crashed the tree
right into the front door,
it also has me
stranded inside until it blows over.
Stuck here with a super cute guy
standing right there in the living room.
Wait a sec… Is this becoming…
a sleepover situation?
[both giggling]
No way he can spend the night.
We barely even know each other.
-Let's go, Anzu!
-[groaning]
-[Anzu] I am so not ready for this…
-Let's go, Anzu! Go!
[Anzu]
This was that thing's plan all along.
[stomach rumbles]
[gasps]
Yeah, I'm hungry too.
-I guess I'd better make some dinner.
-You're sure?
[Anzu] Consider it a thank you
for getting rid of that bug.
Problem is… what do I make?
Let me see here.
Maybe I can grill something
that's not overly fancy.
-A chance to earn girlfriend points.
-[groans]
[grunts]
[grunting continues]
[yelps]
This whole night!
You set all this up, didn't you?
Well, duh.
[groans]
You even planted that bug!
Sure, but thanks to me,
your evening is about to heat up.
Ugh, this is all your fault.
Not gonna lie, I was hoping
it would turn out like this.
-I'm so scared.
-I've got you.
[Riri] I got to say,
I didn't think you'd tackle him.
[chuckles]
And that scream, like a bad word game.
Shut up! I'll have you know
my scream is perfectly normal.
[Riri] I was pretty impressed
that you were able to get him
on the floor so easily.
That was a steamy moment
in the making, but no.
Are you seriously judging me?
Look!
-You're the one causing all this trouble.
-[thunder clapping]
Don't fret.
I got everything under control.
[Anzu] You call that "under control"?
[Riri] I can fix that. No problem.
Chill up. It's time to blow him away
with your cooking skills.
Remember, the way to a man's heart
is through his stomach.
[Anzu] I only know how to cook stir-fry.
Stir-fry? That's perfect!
[laughs]
You can make Caprese sautée chicken?
Or blue crab with eggs and sauce?
Get real!
[gasps]
Why would I bother making
a good impression on this guy, anyway?
MISO, SOY SAUCE
Do you want miso or soy sauce?
Miso.
I handed you romance on a silver platter!
[Riri screams]
[Tsukasa] Thanks for dinner.
Oh, man.
Hmm…
I'm here to grant girls like you
who reject all opportunities of romance
a chance to experience love
through this dating game.
[Anzu] If that thing is causing all this,
it's a safe bet
the storm won't let up till morning.
You picked the wrong girl to mess with.
You wanna play? Let's play.
[pants]
-[Anzu] Kazuki!
-Huh?
-[thunderclaps]
-Spend the night.
Yeah, I think I'll pass on that.
Do not fear.
There'll be no funny business.
[Tsukasa] That's, uh, reassuring.
Great! It's settled then.
Bath time! I'll fill up the tub.
Huh?
Uh…
[light music]
[Anzu] Here, these are my dad's,
but they should fit you.
[Tsukasa] Thanks.
You don't want to go first?
Of course not. Guests always go first.
Hm.
[giggles]
I knew you couldn't resist forever.
Now, you're spending the night together.
Next stop, romance!
[evil laughter]
Hmm.
So, I'll take the couch.
This blanket should be warm enough.
Huh?
Thanks for the bath, Hoshino.
[Anzu] No worries.
Oh, you didn't change your shirt?
-Yeah, not really my style.
-[meows]
It was the only one I could find for you.
It would have been
kind of funny to see it on.
[Anzu exhales]
That's much better!
Ah…
-So lame!
What's with the tucked-in shirt?
You are not making this easy on me.
You're the one who told me to bundle up.
Consider it boy repellent. No chance
for romance when I'm dressed like this.
Oh, no. Is she kidding…
Abandoning all of her self-respect
to resist romance.
So, Kazuki, wanna play a little game?
[Tsukasa] What game?
[Anzu] How about these?
I can't play them alone, you know.
Okay. But I'm pretty good at these.
Great! A worthy challenger.
This should be really fun.
What?
[groaning]
Uh, ugh…
Ooh…
-All right!
-Why can't I beat you?
[laughs]
You're gonna have to put in a lot
more work if you wanna beat me at games.
[Tsukasa] You don't have
to be a brat about it.
-Ugh…
-Huh?
I challenge you to a game of luck.
Let's see how you do
without your strategies.
Ha! Fine, but whoever loses
has to make lunch,
and I'll take two desserts, thanks.
-Slow down there.
-[Anzu] Game on, you're going down.
I am gonna be a billionaire.
[laughs]
[Riri] On that stormy night
at the Hoshino house,
an epic board game battle began.
Anzu, in her frumpiest PJ's,
completely ignoring a chance of romance.
Kazuki with his best poker face,
seeking revenge.
Each player oblivious to the situation.
Each determined to be the winner!
[Anzu] Hm.
[rattling, chiming]
[Anzu] Hm, hm, hm, hm, hm…
Hm?
"You damaged a luxury car.
Pay 10,000 dollars."?
I'm in debt already!
-[wails]
-[scoffs]
[game spinner rattling]
[Tsukasa] Hm, hm…
"You found an antique vase.
Collect the five-thousand-dollar reward."
[Anzu] Who loses something like that?
Grrr.
-[grunts]
-[game spinner rattling]
"The gambling habit caught up to you.
You lose all your money
at the races." Seriously?
[groans, sighs]
[Tsukasa] Hm, hm, hm…
"You sold your macho men figures
to a collector. Earn 50,000 dollars."
Come on! It's not fair!
You're landing on all the good stuff.
Hey, don't blame me.
Luck's on my side tonight.
[gasps]
[evil laughter]
[Anzu] So, that's how you wanna play?
Grr. I will not lose!
"You step in dog poop
and ruined your Jimmy Choo's.
Replace them for 10,000 dollars."
Who wears expensive shoes
like that to walk their dogs?
"The shock of stepping in dog poop
makes you drop 10,000 dollars."
[screams]
No!
Hm?
"You dog, Pochi,
dug up Tokugawa's buried treasure.
Collect one million dollars."
-[Anzu] What?
-[Tsukasa] Good boy, Pochi.
[Anzu grunts]
…two, three, four.
"You step in dog poop
and ruined your Jimmy Choo's.
Replace them for 10,000 dollars."
Not again!
[Tsukasa] How many times
you're gonna step in poop?
-Yeah? Laugh it up! Go on!
-[Tsukasa giggles]
[Anzu] Your dog's probably the one leaving
all that poop on my side of the street!
Don't accuse my Pochi like that.
[miniature plane tapping]
Huh? Guess I won.
What?
Didn't have to put in that much more work
in order to beat you after all.
[grunts angrily]
Looks like Anzu lost. Too bad!
-I'll show you!
-[grunts]
[Anzu] This is such a drag.
Why did I have to go
and open my big mouth?
Huh?
I thought I should help…
since I lost the first game.
[gasps]
Thank you!
Feel free to use whatever
is in the fridge.
You're the best!
Come on, you have to
at least make something.
-I mean you are the loser.
-[sighs]
Don't rub it in.
[Tsukasa] Do you always
put sugar in your eggs?
Of course. That's how you make it.
-Probably pineapple in your pork?
-Duh.
-Potato apple salad?
-Delicious!
[sighs]
You really are a weirdo.
[Anzu] Weird or not,
I'm the one making the eggs,
so I'll prepare them
how I like them, plain and simple.
[sizzling]
[humming]
[humming angrily]
[growling]
Huh? Is that supposed
to be scrambled eggs?
[Anzu] For your information,
they don't always turn out this bad.
Maybe you just need
a little more practice.
[Anzu sighs]
[Anzu] Kazuki, these look delicious!
Ah, mm.
Mmm… Mm!
These are crazy good!
Who knew you are such a pro.
Well, I've been working part-time
in the kitchen of a local bar.
Slow down.
Save some for lunch for tomorrow.
[in muffled voice]
What? I'm hungry.
A girl can't live
on instant noodles alone.
-I guess I should have made more.
-Hm…
Or you can make some extra now,
so I can have some more tomorrow.
Hm.
-[Anzu] Don't be shy. Use the whole bag!
-Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
[Tsukasa] Stop! That's too much.
[Anzu] Looks so good!
[yelps, chuckles]
Oh, man! You even made octopus!
You can't have homemade lunch
without octopus.
[Anzu] Hmm…
[Anzu] He's not at all
what I thought he was
from my first impression.
[bright music]
Everyone thinks he's this standoffish guy
but he's actually pretty easy to talk to.
I feel like I could tell him anything.
[gasps]
I am not developing feelings for him.
Not that he's interested.
Besides, I haven't earned
any girlfriend points.
[Anzu] How about I beat you
at a game of cards next?
-Okay, just gotta use the restroom first.
-Sounds good.
[Anzu] When did it get so late?
I'm not even tired.
We can play Speed or Concentration.
[squeals]
So many options.
-[Riri] What are you doing?
-Ugh, you again?
Why are you wasting time
playing games like a bunch of little kids?
Watch a rom-com, flirt.
Give in to the romance of it all.
-No one asked you!
-Oh, sad.
You couldn't even achieve the classic
-run-into-each-other-in-the-bath scene.
-Grr.
Try it and you and that wand
will get better acquainted.
So, maybe I should have cast
that spell on you after all.
[scoffs]
Sorry to disappoint,
but there is no chance this goes your way.
-Really?
-[yells]
Ow!
It's time for all good children
to go to sleep.
-What?
-[snores]
Looks like she passed out. That was fast!
Hoshino, if you're gonna sleep,
go to your room. Wake up!
Hm.
Now, what'd I do?
Hm?
Shouldn't sleep with your glasses on.
[moans]
[grunts]
Mmm…
Momohiki, I'll never let go, ever!
Momohiki? Who the heck is that?
-[Anzu grunts]
-[Tsukasa] What a grip!
[sighs]
Jeez.
I haven't had
that much fun in a long time.
[cheerful music]
-[chuckles]
-[snores]
What a weirdo.
A fanfare, please!
And a big congratulations!
Did you fall for my little trick?
I bet now you don't feel like
skipping the ending, right?
In today's world, you can watch
whatever you want at your own convenience.
But don't you think in that process
we've also lost something?
[sighs]
Don't just let things be! Come on!
Let's go on a super-duper happy adventure!
So I can make sure I get paid.
[closing theme music]
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Lo-love! ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪
In today's world, you can watch
whatever you want at your own convenience.
But don't you think in that process
we've also lost something?
[sighs]
Don't just let things be! Come on!
Let's go on a super-duper happy adventure!
So I can make sure I get paid.
[closing theme music]
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Lo-love! ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪